{
    "id": "869408c2f0f740dfadcf8ca7162b4b04",
    "title": "Leave, Take Or Make",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The company ……………………. shirts and trousers.",
            "description": "We use the word make to talk about producing something. ",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "takes",
                "leaves"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7fdc0d3417494e0187556b9734acdbee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t ……………………… trouble.",
            "description": "To make trouble is to cause trouble.",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "make",
                "leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "576fb9fd4c754666910846d2432f432d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The circus …………………………. town this morning.",
            "description": "To leave town is to go away from the town.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "made",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "49d6f7eaa431469fab6166e6adfbfe4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cigarette ……………………………. a bad taste in my mouth.",
            "description": "To leave a bad taste is to cause a bad taste.",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "made",
                "took"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e9a9e52c92341e498e5ef1b5161440d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hurry or you won’t …………………….. the train.",
            "description": "To make the train is to arrive in time for the train. ",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "take",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d353f8948f3b471f9fcbf294eb3a9490"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ………………………….. most of his money to charity.",
            "description": "Leave means bequeath here.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "made",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "473b1fdb77e242a586df7c7cc48a34bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………….. a wife and three grown sons.",
            "description": "Here leave means be survived by.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "made",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ebaf49de09514bee817a2fb3bc4d3400"
        },
        {
            "question": "The military …………………….. control of the government.",
            "description": "To take control is to seize control.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "made",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "548ea03af37b43f493bc5ea2feed4775"
        },
        {
            "question": "When buying a coat, look closely at its ……………………….",
            "description": "Make can mean brand.",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e50d41ec14145d8b0b2345689c93846"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. the rope in your right hand and pull.",
            "description": "Take means grab here.",
            "answers": [
                "Take",
                "Make",
                "Leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96613d3f1f144b8db1205a45fe993c35"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have to ………………………. Rome by sunset.",
            "description": "Make means reach or arrive at here.",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "take"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "955336fb43724b7bb40e2a9354716df4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Becoming a doctor ……………………….. years of study.",
            "description": "Here take means requires or demands.",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "leaves",
                "takes"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "38ccd6974ac3437984fd811259626b70"
        }
    ]
}